Loading...

Terms of Service & Privacy Policy
=================================

**Contact us on all site issues: info\[at\]adultfilmindex.com**

Your privacy is important to us.

At Adult Film Index, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit Adult Film Index, and how we safeguard your information. We will never sell your personal information to third parties.

Log Files

We collect and use the data contained in our web server log files. The information in the log files include your IP address, the browser you used to visit our site, the time you visited our site and which pages you viewed.

Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information. This could include the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. We also use third party advertisements on Adult Film Index to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.

You can choose to disable our or third-party cookies in your browser settings. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

**Adult Film Index** © Copyright 2024. All rights reserved. | [Terms of Service](https://adultfilmindex.com/terms) | [Privacy Policy](https://adultfilmindex.com/terms)  
Find a mistake on our data? Please [report it](https://adultfilmindex.com/about). | [Advertise here](https://trafokit.com/i884.info)
